<?xml version='1.0'?>
<!--Public Register-->
<Registration>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>ZA025553</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>ADIDAS (U.K.) LIMITED</Organisation_name>
    <Companies_House_number>01075951</Companies_House_number>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>THE ADIDAS CENTRE</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>PEPPER ROAD, HAZEL GROVE</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_3>STOCKPORT</Organisation_address_line_3>
    <Organisation_address_line_4>CHESHIRE.</Organisation_address_line_4>
    <Organisation_postcode>SK7 5SA</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2013-12-06</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-12-05</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>N</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<B><FONT size=2 face=verdana><P>Nature of work - Retail/Wholesale</P>  <P><Br></P> <P>Description of processing</P></B> <P>The following is a broad description of the way this organisation/data controller processes personal information. To understand how your own personal information is processed you may need to refer to any personal communications you have received, check any privacy notices the organisation has provided or contact the organisation to ask about your personal circumstances. </P>  <P><Br></P><B> <P>Reasons/purposes for processing information</P></B> <P>We process personal information to enable us to buy, sell, promote and advertise our products and services; maintain our own accounts and records; support and manage our employees; the trading and sharing of personal information; the use of CCTV systems for crime prevention.</P>  <P><Br></P><B> <P>Type/classes of information processed</P></B> <P>We process information relevant to the above reasons/purposes. This may include:</P> <UL> <LI> personal details</LI> <LI> family details</LI> <LI> lifestyle and social circumstances</LI> <LI> education and employment details</LI> <LI> financial details</LI> <LI> goods and services</LI></UL>  <P><Br></P> <P>We also process sensitive classes of information that may include: </P> <UL> <LI> racial or ethnic origin</LI> <LI> religious or other beliefs</LI> <LI> trade union membership</LI> <LI> physical or mental health details</LI> <LI> offences and alleged offences</LI> <LI> visual images, personal appearance and behaviour</LI> <LI> criminal proceedings and behaviour</LI></UL>  <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information is processed about</P></B> <P>We process personal information about: </P> <UL> <LI> employees</LI> <LI> customers</LI> <LI> suppliers</LI> <LI> service providers</LI> <LI> enquirers, complainants</LI> <LI> offenders and suspected offenders</LI> <LI> individuals captured by CCTV images</LI></UL>  <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information may be shared with</P></B> <P>We sometimes need to share the personal information we process with the individual themself and also with other organisations. Where this is necessary we are required to comply with all aspects of the Data Protection Act (DPA). What follows is a description of the types of organisations we may need to share some of the personal information we process with for one or more reasons. </P>  <P><Br></P> <P>Where necessary or required we share information with: </P> <UL> <LI> employees</LI> <LI> customers</LI> <LI> suppliers</LI> <LI> family, associates and representatives of the person whose personal data we are processing</LI> <LI> services providers</LI> <LI> current, past and prospective employers</LI> <LI> business associates</LI> <LI> financial organisations</LI> <LI> recruitment and employment agencies</LI> <LI> educators and examining bodies</LI> <LI> other companies in the same group</LI> <LI> credit reference agencies</LI> <LI> debt collection and tracing agencies</LI> <LI> central government</LI> <LI> traders in personal data</LI> <LI>police forces and security organisations</LI></UL></FONT><P><BR></P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><B>
<P>CCTV - Crime Prevention and/or Staff Monitoring </B></P>
<P>CCTV is used for maintaining the security of property and premises and for preventing and investigating crime, it may also be used to monitor staff when carrying out work duties. For these reasons the information processed may include visual images, personal appearance and behaviours. This information may be about staff, customers and clients, offenders and suspected offenders, members of the public and those inside, entering or in the immediate vicinity of the area under surveillance. Where necessary or required this information is shared with the data subjects themselves, employees and agents, services providers, police forces, security organisations and persons making an enquiry.</P></FONT><P><BR></P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><B>
<P>Trading and Sharing Personal Information</B></P>
<P>Personal information is traded and shared as a primary business function. For this reason the information processed may include name, contact details, family details, financial details, employment details, and goods and services. This information may be about customers and clients. The information may be traded or shared with business associates and professional advisers, agents, service providers, customers and clients, and traders in personal data.</P></FONT><P><Br></P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><B> <P>Undertaking Research </P></B><P>Personal information is also processed in order to undertake research. For this reason the information processed may include name, contact details, family details, lifestyle and social circumstances, financial details, good and services. The sensitive types of information may include physical or mental health details, racial or ethnic origin and religious or other beliefs. This information is about survey respondents. Where necessary or required this information may be shared with customers and clients, agents, service providers, survey and research organisations.</P></FONT><B><FONT size=2 face=verdana>
<P><BR></P>
<P>Transfers</P>
<P></B>It may sometimes be necessary to transfer personal information overseas. When this is needed information may be transferred to countries or territories around the world. Any transfers made will be in full compliance with all aspects of the data protection act.</P></FONT>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
</Registration>