    <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z9461314</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>FIND ME A TRADESPERSON</Organisation_name>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>205 COLLIERS BREAK</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>EMERSONS GREEN</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_3>BRISTOL</Organisation_address_line_3>
    <Organisation_postcode>BS16 7ED</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-05-22</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-05-21</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>Y</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<B><FONT size=2 face=verdana><P>Nature of work - Consultant</P></B> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Description of processing</P></B> <P>The following is a broad description of the way this organisation/data controller processes personal information. To understand how your own personal information is processed you may need to refer to any personal communications you have received, check any privacy notices the organisation has provided or contact the organisation to ask about your personal circumstances. </P><B> <P><Br></P> <P>Reasons/purposes for processing information</P></B> <P>We process personal information to enable us to provide consultancy and advisory services, to promote our services, to maintain our own accounts and records and to support and manage our employees.</P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Type/classes of information processed</P></B> <P>We process information relating to the above reasons/purposes. This information may include:</P> <UL> <LI>personal details</LI> <LI>family, lifestyle and social circumstances</LI> <LI>business activities of the person whose personal information we are processing</LI> <LI>goods and services provided</LI> <LI>financial details</LI> <LI>education details</LI> <LI>employment details</LI></UL> <P><Br></P> <P>We also process sensitive classes of information that may include:</P> <UL> <LI>physical or mental health details</LI> <LI>offences and alleged offences</LI> <LI>racial or ethnic origin</LI> <LI>religious or other beliefs of a similar nature</LI></UL><B> <P><Br></P> <P>Who the information is processed about</P></B> <P>We process personal information about our customers, clients and employees, complainants and enquirers, suppliers, advisers and other professional experts.</P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information may be shared with</P></B> <P>We sometimes need to share the personal information we process with the individual themself and also with other organisations. Where this is necessary we are required to comply with all aspects of the Data Protection Act (DPA). What follows is a description of the types of organisations we may need to share some of the personal information we process with for one or more reasons. </P> <P><Br></P> <P>Where necessary or required we share information with:</P> <UL> <LI>business associates and other professional advisers </LI> <LI>family, associates and representatives of the person whose personal data we are processing</LI> <LI>financial organisations</LI> <LI>current, past or prospective employers</LI> <LI>educators and examining bodies</LI> <LI>suppliers and services providers</LI> <LI>traders in personal data</LI></UL></FONT><P><BR></P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><B>
<P>Trading and Sharing Personal Information</B></P>
<P>Personal information is traded and shared as a primary business function. For this reason the information processed may include name, contact details, family details, financial details, employment details, and goods and services. This information may be about customers and clients. The information may be traded or shared with business associates and professional advisers, agents, service providers, customers and clients, and traders in personal data.</P></FONT><B><FONT size=2 face=verdana>
<P><BR></P>
<P>Transfers</B></P>
<P>It may sometimes be necessary to transfer personal information overseas. When this is needed information is only shared within the European Economic Area (EEA). Any transfers made will be in full compliance with all aspects of the data protection act.</P></FONT>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z9461299</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>THE ARSENAL FOOTBALL CLUB PLC</Organisation_name>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>HIGHBURY HOUSE</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>75 DRAYTON PARK</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_3>LONDON</Organisation_address_line_3>
    <Organisation_postcode>N5 1BU</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-05-08</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-05-07</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>N</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 1</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff Administration</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Appointments or removals, pay, discipline, superannuation, work management or other personnel matters in relation to the staff of the data controller.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff including volunteers, agents, temporary and casual workers<br>Relatives, guardians and associates of the data subject<br>Advisers, consultants and other professional experts</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Education and Training Details<br>Employment Details<br>Financial Details<br>Racial or Ethnic Origin<br>Religious or Other Beliefs Of A Similar Nature<br>Trade Union Membership<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Relatives, guardians or other persons associated with the data subject<br>Current, past or prospective employers of the data subject<br>Healthcare, social and welfare advisers or practitioners<br>Education, training establishments and examining bodies<br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Persons making an enquiry or complaint<br>Financial organisations and advisers<br>Trade, employer associations and professional bodies<br>Local Government<br>Central Government<br>Voluntary and charitable organisations<br>The media<br>Data processors<br>Employment and recruitment agencies<br>Tenants</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Worldwide</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 2</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Advertising, Marketing & Public Relations</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Advertising or marketing the business of the data controller, activity, goods or services and promoting public relations in connection with that business or activity, or those goods or services.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff including volunteers, agents, temporary and casual workers<br>Customers and Clients<br>Suppliers<br>Members or supporters<br>Complainants, correspondents and enquirers<br>Relatives, guardians and associates of the data subject<br>Advisers, consultants and other professional experts<br>Students and pupils</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Employment Details<br>Goods or Services Provided<br>Racial or Ethnic Origin<br>Religious or Other Beliefs Of A Similar Nature<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Relatives, guardians or other persons associated with the data subject<br>Current, past or prospective employers of the data subject<br>Healthcare, social and welfare advisers or practitioners<br>Education, training establishments and examining bodies<br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Other companies in the same group as the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Persons making an enquiry or complaint<br>Financial organisations and advisers<br>Credit reference agencies<br>Survey and research organisations<br>Local Government<br>Central Government<br>Voluntary and charitable organisations<br>The media<br>Data processors</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Worldwide</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 3</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Accounts & Records</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Keeping accounts related to any business or other activity carried on by the data controller, or deciding whether to accept any person as a customer or supplier, or keeping records of purchases, sales or other transactions for the purpose of ensuring that the requisite payments and deliveries are made or services provided by him or to him in respect of those transactions, or for the purpose of making financial or management forecasts to assist him in the conduct of any such business or activity</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff including volunteers, agents, temporary and casual workers<br>Customers and Clients<br>Suppliers<br>Members or supporters<br>Advisers, consultants and other professional experts<br>Students and pupils</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Employment Details<br>Financial Details</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Financial organisations and advisers<br>Credit reference agencies<br>Debt collection and tracing agencies<br>Trade, employer associations and professional bodies<br>Data processors</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Worldwide</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 4</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Administration of Membership Records</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>The administration of membership records.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Members or supporters</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Education and Training Details<br>Employment Details<br>Financial Details<br>Goods or Services Provided<br>Racial or Ethnic Origin<br>Religious or Other Beliefs Of A Similar Nature<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition<br>Offences (Including Alleged Offences)</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Relatives, guardians or other persons associated with the data subject<br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Other companies in the same group as the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Debt collection and tracing agencies<br>Survey and research organisations<br>Police forces<br>Private investigators<br>Local Government<br>Central Government<br>Data processors</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Worldwide</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 5</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Crime Prevention and Prosecution of Offenders</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Crime prevention and detection and the apprehension and prosecution of offenders.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff including volunteers, agents, temporary and casual workers<br>Customers and Clients<br>Suppliers<br>Members or supporters<br>Complainants, correspondents and enquirers<br>Relatives, guardians and associates of the data subject<br>Advisers, consultants and other professional experts<br>Students and pupils<br>Offenders and suspected offenders</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>THOSE INISDE, ENTERING OR IN THE IMMEDIATE VICINITY OF THE AREA UNDER SURVEILLAN</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Education and Training Details<br>Employment Details<br>Financial Details<br>Goods or Services Provided<br>Racial or Ethnic Origin<br>Religious or Other Beliefs Of A Similar Nature<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition<br>Offences (Including Alleged Offences)</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>SOUNDS AND/OR VISUAL IMAGES</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Relatives, guardians or other persons associated with the data subject<br>Current, past or prospective employers of the data subject<br>Healthcare, social and welfare advisers or practitioners<br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Other companies in the same group as the data controller<br>Survey and research organisations<br>Police forces<br>Private investigators<br>Local Government<br>Central Government<br>Data processors</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Worldwide</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 7</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Education</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>The provision of education or training as a primary function or as a business activity.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Customers and Clients<br>Members or supporters<br>Students and pupils</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Education and Training Details<br>Racial or Ethnic Origin<br>Religious or Other Beliefs Of A Similar Nature<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition<br>Offences (Including Alleged Offences)</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Relatives, guardians or other persons associated with the data subject<br>Healthcare, social and welfare advisers or practitioners<br>Education, training establishments and examining bodies<br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Survey and research organisations<br>Local Government<br>Central Government<br>Voluntary and charitable organisations<br>The media<br>Data processors</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Worldwide</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 8</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Information and Databank Administration</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Maintenance of information or databanks as a reference tool or general resource.This includes catalogues, lists, directories and bibliographic data. bases.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff including volunteers, agents, temporary and casual workers<br>Customers and Clients<br>Suppliers<br>Members or supporters<br>Complainants, correspondents and enquirers<br>Relatives, guardians and associates of the data subject<br>Advisers, consultants and other professional experts<br>Students and pupils<br>Offenders and suspected offenders</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Education and Training Details<br>Employment Details<br>Financial Details<br>Goods or Services Provided<br>Racial or Ethnic Origin<br>Religious or Other Beliefs Of A Similar Nature<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition<br>Offences (Including Alleged Offences)</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 9</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Journalism and Media</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Publication by any data controller in relation to journalism, artistic or literary purposes made or intended to be made available to the public or any section of the public.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff including volunteers, agents, temporary and casual workers<br>Customers and Clients<br>Suppliers<br>Members or supporters<br>Complainants, correspondents and enquirers<br>Advisers, consultants and other professional experts<br>Students and pupils<br>Offenders and suspected offenders</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Education and Training Details<br>Goods or Services Provided<br>Racial or Ethnic Origin<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition<br>Offences (Including Alleged Offences)<br>Criminal Proceedings, Outcomes And Sentences.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Relatives, guardians or other persons associated with the data subject<br>The media</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Worldwide</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 10</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Licensing and Registration</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>The administration of licensing or maintenance of official registers.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Customers and Clients<br>Suppliers</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>LICENSEES</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Worldwide</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 11</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Property Management</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>The management and administration of land, property and residential property and the estate management of other organisations.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Customers and Clients<br>Suppliers</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Local Government<br>Central Government<br>Data processors<br>Tenants</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 12</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Trading / Sharing in Personal Information</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>The sale, hire or exchange of personal information.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff including volunteers, agents, temporary and casual workers<br>Customers and Clients<br>Members or supporters<br>Complainants, correspondents and enquirers<br>Advisers, consultants and other professional experts<br>Students and pupils<br>Offenders and suspected offenders</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Education and Training Details<br>Employment Details<br>Financial Details<br>Goods or Services Provided<br>Racial or Ethnic Origin<br>Religious or Other Beliefs Of A Similar Nature<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition<br>Offences (Including Alleged Offences)<br>Criminal Proceedings, Outcomes And Sentences.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Trade, employer associations and professional bodies</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Worldwide</FONT></P><hr>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z9461285</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>THE TRUSTEES OF THE CCB PENSION FUND</Organisation_name>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>REDSWAN PENSIONEERS LTD</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>ARC HOUSE</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_3>60 GLOUCESTER ROAD</Organisation_address_line_3>
    <Organisation_address_line_4>URMSTON</Organisation_address_line_4>
    <Organisation_address_line_5>MANCHESTER</Organisation_address_line_5>
    <Organisation_postcode>M41 9AE</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-04-28</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-04-27</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>Y</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 1</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Pensions Administration</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>The administration of funded pensions or superannuation schemes.  Data controllers using this purpose will usually be the trustees of pension funds.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff including volunteers, agents, temporary and casual workers<br>Customers and Clients<br>Suppliers<br>Complainants, correspondents and enquirers<br>Relatives, guardians and associates of the data subject<br>Advisers, consultants and other professional experts<br>Employees of other organisations<br>Employers</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>MEMBERS AND BENEFICIARIES<br>TRUSTEES</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Employment Details<br>Financial Details<br>Goods or Services Provided<br>Trade Union Membership<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition<br>Sexual Life<br>Criminal Proceedings, Outcomes And Sentences.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Relatives, guardians or other persons associated with the data subject<br>Current, past or prospective employers of the data subject<br>Healthcare, social and welfare advisers or practitioners<br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Other companies in the same group as the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Persons making an enquiry or complaint<br>Financial organisations and advisers<br>Credit reference agencies<br>Debt collection and tracing agencies<br>Survey and research organisations<br>Trade, employer associations and professional bodies<br>Police forces<br>Private investigators<br>Local Government<br>Central Government<br>Voluntary and charitable organisations<br>Ombudsmen and regulatory authorities<br>Data processors<br>Claimants, beneficiaries, assignees, payees</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z9461254</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>MARY CREAGH MP</Organisation_name>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>20-22 CHEAPSIDE</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>WAKEFIELD</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_3>WEST YORKSHIRE</Organisation_address_line_3>
    <Organisation_postcode>WF1 2TF</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-05-08</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-05-07</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>N</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 1</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Constituency Casework</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>The carrying out of casework on behalf of individual constituents</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Controllers further description of Purpose:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>THE CARRYING OUT OF CASEWORK ON BEHALF  OF INDIVIDUAL CONSTITUENTS</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Relatives, guardians and associates of the data subject<br>Business or other contacts</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>CONSTITUENTS<br>SUBJECT OF COMPLAINTS<br>COMPLAINANTS, CORRESPONDENTS AND ENQUIRERS</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Employment Details<br>Financial Details<br>Racial or Ethnic Origin<br>Political Opinions<br>Trade Union Membership<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition<br>Offences (Including Alleged Offences)</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>HOUSING DETAILS<br>DETAILS OF COMPLAINT, PROBLEM OR ISSUE</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>SUBJECT OF COMPLAINT, PROBLEM OR ISSUE<br>OTHER STATUTORY LAW ENFORCEMENT AGENCIES, INVESTIGATING BODIES<br>ELECTED REPRESENTATIVES<br>OTHER HOLDERS OF PUBLIC OFFICE<br>LANDLORDS</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Relatives, guardians or other persons associated with the data subject<br>Healthcare, social and welfare advisers or practitioners<br>Local Government<br>Central Government<br>Political organisations<br>The media</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 2</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff, Agent and Contractor Administration</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff including volunteers, agents, temporary and casual workers<br>Relatives, guardians and associates of the data subject</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Education and Training Details<br>Employment Details<br>Financial Details<br>Racial or Ethnic Origin<br>Religious or Other Beliefs Of A Similar Nature<br>Trade Union Membership<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>EMPLOYMENT AND RECRUITMENT AGENCIES</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Relatives, guardians or other persons associated with the data subject<br>Current, past or prospective employers of the data subject<br>Education, training establishments and examining bodies<br>Financial organisations and advisers<br>Central Government</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z946121X</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>THE TRUSTEES OF THE GAP INTERNATIONAL LTD DPS</Organisation_name>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>EGAN ROBERTS FINANCIAL SERVICES LIMITED</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>GLENFIELD HOUSE</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_3>PHILIPS ROAD</Organisation_address_line_3>
    <Organisation_address_line_4>BLACKBURN</Organisation_address_line_4>
    <Organisation_postcode>BB1 5PF</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-04-28</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-04-27</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>Y</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 1</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Pensions Administration</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>The administration of funded pensions or superannuation schemes.  Data controllers using this purpose will usually be the trustees of pension funds.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff including volunteers, agents, temporary and casual workers<br>Customers and Clients<br>Suppliers<br>Complainants, correspondents and enquirers<br>Relatives, guardians and associates of the data subject<br>Advisers, consultants and other professional experts<br>Employees of other organisations<br>Employers</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>MEMBERS AND BENEFICIARIES<br>TRUSTEES</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Employment Details<br>Financial Details<br>Goods or Services Provided<br>Trade Union Membership<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition<br>Sexual Life<br>Criminal Proceedings, Outcomes And Sentences.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Relatives, guardians or other persons associated with the data subject<br>Current, past or prospective employers of the data subject<br>Healthcare, social and welfare advisers or practitioners<br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Other companies in the same group as the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Persons making an enquiry or complaint<br>Financial organisations and advisers<br>Credit reference agencies<br>Debt collection and tracing agencies<br>Survey and research organisations<br>Trade, employer associations and professional bodies<br>Police forces<br>Private investigators<br>Local Government<br>Central Government<br>Voluntary and charitable organisations<br>Ombudsmen and regulatory authorities<br>Data processors<br>Claimants, beneficiaries, assignees, payees</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z9461194</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>KENNETH KELLY</Organisation_name>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>OFFICE 4</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>2 LOWER AUCHINGRAMONT ROAD</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_3>HAMILTON</Organisation_address_line_3>
    <Organisation_postcode>ML3 6HW</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-05-08</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-05-07</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>N</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Trading_names>PREMIER CHOICE MORTGAGES</Trading_names>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 1</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff Administration</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Appointments or removals, pay, discipline, superannuation, work management or other personnel matters in relation to the staff of the data controller.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff including volunteers, agents, temporary and casual workers<br>Relatives, guardians and associates of the data subject</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Education and Training Details<br>Employment Details<br>Financial Details<br>Racial or Ethnic Origin<br>Religious or Other Beliefs Of A Similar Nature<br>Trade Union Membership<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Relatives, guardians or other persons associated with the data subject<br>Current, past or prospective employers of the data subject<br>Education, training establishments and examining bodies<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Financial organisations and advisers<br>Central Government<br>Employment and recruitment agencies</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 2</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Advertising, Marketing & Public Relations</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Advertising or marketing the business of the data controller, activity, goods or services and promoting public relations in connection with that business or activity, or those goods or services.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Customers and Clients<br>Complainants, correspondents and enquirers<br>Advisers, consultants and other professional experts</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Goods or Services Provided</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 3</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Accounts & Records</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Keeping accounts related to any business or other activity carried on by the data controller, or deciding whether to accept any person as a customer or supplier, or keeping records of purchases, sales or other transactions for the purpose of ensuring that the requisite payments and deliveries are made or services provided by him or to him in respect of those transactions, or for the purpose of making financial or management forecasts to assist him in the conduct of any such business or activity</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Customers and Clients<br>Suppliers<br>Complainants, correspondents and enquirers</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Financial Details<br>Goods or Services Provided</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Other companies in the same group as the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Financial organisations and advisers<br>Credit reference agencies<br>Debt collection and tracing agencies<br>Central Government</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 4</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Debt Administration and Factoring</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>The tracing of consumer and commercial debtors and the collection on behalf of creditors.  The purchasing of trade debts, including rentals and instalment credit payments, from business.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Customers and Clients<br>Relatives, guardians and associates of the data subject</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Goods or Services Provided<br>Offences (Including Alleged Offences)</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Relatives, guardians or other persons associated with the data subject<br>Current, past or prospective employers of the data subject<br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Other companies in the same group as the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Credit reference agencies<br>Debt collection and tracing agencies<br>Traders in personal data<br>Central Government<br>Courts / Tribunals</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 5</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Provision of Financial Services & Advice</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>The provision of services as an intermediary in respect of any financial transactions including mortgage and insurance broking.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Customers and Clients<br>Relatives, guardians and associates of the data subject</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Financial Details<br>Goods or Services Provided<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Current, past or prospective employers of the data subject<br>Healthcare, social and welfare advisers or practitioners<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Financial organisations and advisers<br>Credit reference agencies<br>Trade, employer associations and professional bodies<br>Central Government<br>Ombudsmen and regulatory authorities</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z9461146</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>IMPEY SHOWERS LTD</Organisation_name>
    <Companies_House_number>3742299</Companies_House_number>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>THE CONQUEST BUSINESS PARK</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>ILTON</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_3>ILMINSTER</Organisation_address_line_3>
    <Organisation_address_line_4>SOMERSET</Organisation_address_line_4>
    <Organisation_postcode>TA19 9EA</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-05-18</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-05-17</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>Y</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<B><FONT size=2 face=verdana><P>Nature of work - Manufacturer</P> <P><Br></P> <P>Description of processing</P></B> <P>The following is a broad description of the way this organisation/data controller processes personal information. To understand how your own personal information is processed you may need to refer to any personal communications you have received, check any privacy notices the organisation has provided or contact the organisation to ask about your personal circumstances. </P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Reasons/purposes for processing information</P></B> <P>We process personal information to enable us to provide manufacturing services, promote our goods and services, maintain our accounts and records and to support and manage our staff. We also process personal information using a CCTV system to maintain the security of the premises and for preventing and investigating crime. </P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Type/classes of information processed</P></B> <P>We process information relevant to the above reasons/purposes. This may include:</P> <UL> <LI>personal details <LI>family details <LI>lifestyle and social circumstances <LI>financial details <LI>employment and education details <LI>goods or services <LI>visual images, personal appearance and behaviour</LI></UL> <P><Br></P> <P>We also process sensitive classes of information that may include:</P> <UL> <LI>physical or mental health details <LI>offences and alleged offences <LI>racial or ethnic origin <LI>religious or other beliefs of a similar nature <LI>trade union membership</LI></UL> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information is processed about</P></B> <P>We process personal information about:</P> <UL> <LI>our employees <LI>customers and clients <LI>suppliers and services providers <LI>advisers, consultants and other professional experts <LI>complainants and enquirers <LI>individuals captured by CCTV images</LI></UL> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information may be shared with</P></B> <P>We sometimes need to share the personal information we process with the individual themself and also with other organisations. Where this is necessary we are required to comply with all aspects of the Data Protection Act (DPA). What follows is a description of the types of organisations we may need to share some of the personal information we process with for one or more reasons. </P> <P><Br></P> <P>Where necessary or required we share information with:</P> <UL> <LI>family, associates and representatives of the person whose personal data we are processing <LI>employment and recruitment agencies <LI>current, past and prospective employers <LI>educators and examining bodies <LI>central government <LI>credit reference agencies <LI>suppliers and service providers <LI>debt collection and tracing agencies <LI>financial organisations <LI>police forces <LI>security organisations</LI></UL></FONT><B><FONT size=2 face=verdana>
<P><BR></P>
<P>Transfers</B></P>
<P>It may sometimes be necessary to transfer personal information overseas. When this is needed information is only shared within the European Economic Area (EEA). Any transfers made will be in full compliance with all aspects of the data protection act.</P></FONT>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z9461132</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>THE TRUSTEES OF THE JOE CUMMINGS LTD PENSION FUND</Organisation_name>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>REDSWAN PENSIONEERS LTD</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>ARC HOUSE</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_3>60 GLOUCESTER ROAD</Organisation_address_line_3>
    <Organisation_address_line_4>URMSTON</Organisation_address_line_4>
    <Organisation_address_line_5>MANCHESTER</Organisation_address_line_5>
    <Organisation_postcode>M41 9AE</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-04-28</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-04-27</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>Y</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 1</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Pensions Administration</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>The administration of funded pensions or superannuation schemes.  Data controllers using this purpose will usually be the trustees of pension funds.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff including volunteers, agents, temporary and casual workers<br>Customers and Clients<br>Suppliers<br>Complainants, correspondents and enquirers<br>Relatives, guardians and associates of the data subject<br>Advisers, consultants and other professional experts<br>Employees of other organisations<br>Employers</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>MEMBERS AND BENEFICIARIES<br>TRUSTEES</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Employment Details<br>Financial Details<br>Goods or Services Provided<br>Trade Union Membership<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition<br>Sexual Life<br>Criminal Proceedings, Outcomes And Sentences.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Relatives, guardians or other persons associated with the data subject<br>Current, past or prospective employers of the data subject<br>Healthcare, social and welfare advisers or practitioners<br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Other companies in the same group as the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Persons making an enquiry or complaint<br>Financial organisations and advisers<br>Credit reference agencies<br>Debt collection and tracing agencies<br>Survey and research organisations<br>Trade, employer associations and professional bodies<br>Police forces<br>Private investigators<br>Local Government<br>Central Government<br>Voluntary and charitable organisations<br>Ombudsmen and regulatory authorities<br>Data processors<br>Claimants, beneficiaries, assignees, payees</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z9461129</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>CHRISTOPHER BAIN</Organisation_name>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>12 ST. JAMES CRESCENT</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>BELTON</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_3>GREAT YARMOUTH</Organisation_address_line_3>
    <Organisation_postcode>NR31 9JN</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-05-08</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-05-07</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>N</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<B><FONT size=2 face=verdana><P>Nature of work - Financial, Mortgage and Insurance Services</P></B> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Description of processing</P></B> <P>The following is a broad description of the way this organisation/data controller processes personal information. To understand how your own personal information is processed you may need to refer to any personal communications you have received, check any privacy notices the organisation has provided or contact the organisation to ask about your personal circumstances. </P><B> <P><Br></P> <P>Reasons/purposes for processing information</P></B> <P>We process personal information to enable us to act as an intermediary for any financial transactions including mortgage and insurance broking, and debt administration to our clients; promote our goods and services; maintain our own accounts and records and to support and manage our staff.</P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Type/classes of information processed</P></B> <P>We process information relevant to the above reasons/purposes. This may include: </P> <UL> <LI>personal details</LI> <LI>family details</LI> <LI>lifestyle and social circumstances</LI> <LI>financial details</LI> <LI>employment and education details</LI> <LI>goods or services provided</LI></UL> <P><Br></P> <P>We also process sensitive classes of information that may include: </P> <UL> <LI>physical or mental health details</LI> <LI>racial or ethnic origin</LI> <LI>religious or other beliefs</LI> <LI>trade union membership</LI> <LI>offences and alleged offences</LI></UL> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information is processed about</P></B> <P>We process personal information about:</P> <UL> <LI>clients</LI> <LI>suppliers</LI> <LI>professional advisers and consultants</LI> <LI>enquirers, complainants</LI> <LI>employees</LI></UL> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information may be shared with</P></B> <P>We sometimes need to share the personal information we process with the individual themself and also with other organisations. Where this is necessary we are required to comply with all aspects of the Data Protection Act (DPA). What follows is a description of the types of organisations we may need to share some of the personal information we process with for one or more reasons. </P> <P><Br></P> <P>Where necessary or required we share information with: </P> <UL> <LI>current, past or prospective employers</LI> <LI>family, associates and representatives of the person whose personal data we are processing</LI> <LI>financial organisations</LI> <LI>business associates and professional advisers</LI> <LI>educators and examining bodies</LI> <LI>employment and recruitment agencies</LI> <LI>healthcare and welfare organisations</LI> <LI>credit reference agencies</LI> <LI>debt collection and tracing agencies</LI> <LI>other companies in the same group</LI> <LI>suppliers and services providers</LI> <LI>trade and employer associations</LI> <LI>central government</LI> <LI>law enforcement and prosecuting authorities</LI> <LI>ombudsmen and regulatory authorities</LI> <LI>traders in personal data</LI> <LI>courts and tribunals</LI></UL></FONT><B><FONT size=2 face=verdana>
<P><BR></P>
<P>Transfers</B></P>
<P>It may sometimes be necessary to transfer personal information overseas. When this is needed information is only shared within the European Economic Area (EEA). Any transfers made will be in full compliance with all aspects of the data protection act.</P></FONT>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z9461115</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>INTENDA UK LTD</Organisation_name>
    <Companies_House_number>5362414</Companies_House_number>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>GATE HOUSE</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>FRETHERNE ROAD</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_3>WELWYN GARDEN CITY</Organisation_address_line_3>
    <Organisation_address_line_4>HERTFORDSHIRE</Organisation_address_line_4>
    <Organisation_postcode>AL8 6NS</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-05-08</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-05-07</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>N</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 1</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff Administration</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Appointments or removals, pay, discipline, superannuation, work management or other personnel matters in relation to the staff of the data controller.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff including volunteers, agents, temporary and casual workers<br>Relatives, guardians and associates of the data subject</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Education and Training Details<br>Employment Details<br>Financial Details<br>Racial or Ethnic Origin<br>Religious or Other Beliefs Of A Similar Nature<br>Trade Union Membership<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Relatives, guardians or other persons associated with the data subject<br>Current, past or prospective employers of the data subject<br>Education, training establishments and examining bodies<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Financial organisations and advisers<br>Central Government<br>Employment and recruitment agencies</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>South Africa</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 2</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Advertising, Marketing & Public Relations</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Advertising or marketing the business of the data controller, activity, goods or services and promoting public relations in connection with that business or activity, or those goods or services.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Customers and Clients<br>Complainants, correspondents and enquirers<br>Advisers, consultants and other professional experts</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Goods or Services Provided</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 3</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Accounts & Records</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Keeping accounts related to any business or other activity carried on by the data controller, or deciding whether to accept any person as a customer or supplier, or keeping records of purchases, sales or other transactions for the purpose of ensuring that the requisite payments and deliveries are made or services provided by him or to him in respect of those transactions, or for the purpose of making financial or management forecasts to assist him in the conduct of any such business or activity</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Customers and Clients<br>Suppliers<br>Complainants, correspondents and enquirers</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Financial Details<br>Goods or Services Provided</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Other companies in the same group as the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Financial organisations and advisers<br>Credit reference agencies<br>Debt collection and tracing agencies<br>Central Government</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 4</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Consultancy and Advisory Services</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Giving advice or rendering professional services.The provision of services of an advisory, consultancy or intermediary nature.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Controllers further description of Purpose:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT / TEST AND DEMONSTRATION</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff including volunteers, agents, temporary and casual workers<br>Customers and Clients</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>DATA SUBJECTS NECESSARY FOR THE DEVELOPMENT, TESTING AND DEMONSTRATION<br>OF THE DATA CONTROLLER'S SOFTWARE.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>CLASSES OF DATA NECESSARY FOR THE DEVELOPMENT, TESTING AND DEMONSTRATION<br>OF THE DATA CONTROLLER'S SOFTWARE</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Other companies in the same group as the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z9461101</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>LANE FINANCIAL SERVICES LLP</Organisation_name>
    <Companies_House_number>OC314757</Companies_House_number>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>25 BILLING ROAD</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>NORTHAMPTON</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_3>.</Organisation_address_line_3>
    <Organisation_postcode>NN1 5AT</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-05-04</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-05-03</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>N</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<B><FONT size=2 face=verdana><P>Nature of work - Independent Financial Adviser</P></B> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Description of processing</P></B> <P>The following is a broad description of the way this organisation/data controller processes personal information. To understand how your own personal information is processed you may need to refer to any personal communications you have received, check any privacy notices the organisation has provided or contact the organisation to ask about your personal circumstances. </P><B> <P><Br></P> <P>Reasons/purposes for processing information</P></B> <P>We process personal information to enable us to provide financial services and advice, to maintain our own accounts and records and to support and manage our employees. </P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Type/classes of information processed</P></B> <P>We process information relating to the above reasons/purposes. This information may include:</P> <UL> <LI>personal details</LI> <LI>family details</LI> <LI>lifestyle and social circumstances</LI> <LI>goods and services</LI> <LI>financial details</LI> <LI>education and employment details</LI></UL> <P><Br></P> <P>We also process sensitive classes of information that may include physical or mental health details, racial or ethnic origin and trade union membership. </P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information is processed about</P></B> <P>We process personal information about our customers, clients and suppliers and our employees. </P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information may be shared with</P></B> <P>We sometimes need to share the personal information we process with the individual themself and also with other organisations. Where this is necessary we are required to comply with all aspects of the Data Protection Act (DPA). What follows is a description of the types of organisations we may need to share some of the personal information we process with for one or more reasons. </P> <P><Br></P> <P>Where necessary or required we share information with:</P> <UL> <LI>financial organisations</LI> <LI>credit reference agencies</LI> <LI>ombudsmen and regulatory authorities</LI> <LI>central government</LI> <LI>healthcare professionals</LI> <LI>social and welfare organisations</LI> <LI>current, past or prospective employers</LI> <LI>examining bodies</LI> <LI>service providers</LI></UL></FONT><B><FONT size=2 face=verdana>
<P><BR></P>
<P>Transfers</B></P>
<P>It may sometimes be necessary to transfer personal information overseas. When this is needed information is only shared within the European Economic Area (EEA). Any transfers made will be in full compliance with all aspects of the data protection act.</P></FONT>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z946109X</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>THE TRUSTEES OF THE ACG PENSION SCHEME 2004</Organisation_name>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>REDSWAN PENSIONEERS LTD</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>ARC HOUSE</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_3>60 GLOUCESTER ROAD</Organisation_address_line_3>
    <Organisation_address_line_4>URMSTON</Organisation_address_line_4>
    <Organisation_address_line_5>MANCHESTER</Organisation_address_line_5>
    <Organisation_postcode>M41 9AE</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-04-28</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-04-27</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>Y</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 1</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Pensions Administration</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>The administration of funded pensions or superannuation schemes.  Data controllers using this purpose will usually be the trustees of pension funds.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff including volunteers, agents, temporary and casual workers<br>Customers and Clients<br>Suppliers<br>Complainants, correspondents and enquirers<br>Relatives, guardians and associates of the data subject<br>Advisers, consultants and other professional experts<br>Employees of other organisations<br>Employers</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>MEMBERS AND BENEFICIARIES<br>TRUSTEES</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Employment Details<br>Financial Details<br>Goods or Services Provided<br>Trade Union Membership<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition<br>Sexual Life<br>Criminal Proceedings, Outcomes And Sentences.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Relatives, guardians or other persons associated with the data subject<br>Current, past or prospective employers of the data subject<br>Healthcare, social and welfare advisers or practitioners<br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Other companies in the same group as the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Persons making an enquiry or complaint<br>Financial organisations and advisers<br>Credit reference agencies<br>Debt collection and tracing agencies<br>Survey and research organisations<br>Trade, employer associations and professional bodies<br>Police forces<br>Private investigators<br>Local Government<br>Central Government<br>Voluntary and charitable organisations<br>Ombudsmen and regulatory authorities<br>Data processors<br>Claimants, beneficiaries, assignees, payees</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z9461086</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>SILVERDALE SPECIAL SCHOOL</Organisation_name>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>LANGDALE GARDENS</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>HOWDON</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_3>WALLSEND</Organisation_address_line_3>
    <Organisation_postcode>NE28 0HG</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-05-05</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-05-04</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>N</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<B><FONT size=2 face=verdana><P>Nature of work - School</P></B> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Description of processing</P></B> <P>The following is a broad description of the way this organisation/data controller processes personal information. To understand how your own personal information is processed you may need to refer to any personal communications you have received, check any privacy notices the organisation has provided or contact the organisation to ask about your personal circumstances. </P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Reasons/purposes for processing information</P></B> <P>We process personal information to enable us to:</P> <P>provide education, training, welfare and educational support services</P> <P>administer school property</P> <P>maintain our own accounts and records</P> <P>carry out fundraising</P> <P>support and manage our employees </P> <P><Br></P> <P>We also use CCTV systems to monitor and collect visual images for security and the prevention of crime. </P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Type/classes of information processed</P></B> <P>We process information relating to the above reasons/purposes. This information may include:</P> <UL> <LI>name and personal details</LI> <LI>family, lifestyle and social circumstances</LI> <LI>financial details</LI> <LI>education details</LI> <LI>employment details</LI> <LI>student and disciplinary records</LI> <LI>vetting checks</LI> <LI>goods and services</LI> <LI>visual images, personal appearance and behaviour</LI></UL> <P><Br></P> <P>We also process sensitive classes of information that may include:</P> <UL> <LI>physical or mental health details</LI> <LI>racial or ethnic origin</LI> <LI>religious or other beliefs of a similar nature</LI> <LI>trade union membership</LI> <LI>sexual life</LI> <LI>offences and alleged offences</LI></UL> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information is processed about</P></B> <P>We process personal information about:</P> <UL> <LI>our students and pupils</LI> <LI>advisers and other professional experts</LI> <LI>school staff</LI> <LI>members of school boards</LI> <LI>donors and potential donors</LI> <LI>suppliers</LI> <LI>complainants and enquirers</LI> <LI>individuals captured by CCTV images </LI></UL> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information may be shared with</P></B> <P>We sometimes need to share the personal information we process with the individual themself and also with other organisations. Where this is necessary we are required to comply with all aspects of the Data Protection Act (DPA). What follows is a description of the types of organisations we may need to share some of the personal information we process with for one or more reasons. </P> <P><Br></P> <P>Where necessary or required we share information with:</P> <UL> <LI>education, training, careers and examining bodies</LI> <LI>school staff and boards</LI> <LI>family, associates and representatives of the person whose personal data we are processing</LI> <LI>local and central government</LI> <LI>healthcare professionals</LI> <LI>social and welfare organisations</LI> <LI>police forces</LI> <LI>courts</LI> <LI>current, past or prospective employers</LI> <LI>voluntary and charitable organisations</LI> <LI>business associates and other professional advisers</LI> <LI>suppliers and service providers</LI> <LI>financial organisations</LI> <LI>security organisations</LI> <LI>press and the media</LI></UL></FONT><P><BR></P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><B>
<P>Trading and Sharing Personal Information</B></P>
<P>Personal information is traded and shared as a primary business function. For this reason the information processed may include name, contact details, family details, financial details, employment details, and goods and services. This information may be about customers and clients. The information may be traded or shared with business associates and professional advisers, agents, service providers, customers and clients, and traders in personal data.</P></FONT><B><FONT size=2 face=verdana>
<P><BR></P>
<P>Transfers</P>
<P></B>It may sometimes be necessary to transfer personal information overseas. When this is needed information may be transferred to countries or territories around the world. Any transfers made will be in full compliance with all aspects of the data protection act.</P></FONT>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z9461072</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>TOTRAX LTD</Organisation_name>
    <Companies_House_number>1965571</Companies_House_number>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>RECTORY FARM</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>LANGRICK</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_3>BOSTON</Organisation_address_line_3>
    <Organisation_address_line_4>LINCOLNSHIRE</Organisation_address_line_4>
    <Organisation_postcode>PE22 7AD</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-05-05</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-05-04</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>N</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 1</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff Administration</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Appointments or removals, pay, discipline, superannuation, work management or other personnel matters in relation to the staff of the data controller.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff including volunteers, agents, temporary and casual workers<br>Relatives, guardians and associates of the data subject</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Education and Training Details<br>Employment Details<br>Financial Details<br>Racial or Ethnic Origin<br>Religious or Other Beliefs Of A Similar Nature<br>Trade Union Membership<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Relatives, guardians or other persons associated with the data subject<br>Current, past or prospective employers of the data subject<br>Education, training establishments and examining bodies<br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Financial organisations and advisers<br>Central Government<br>Employment and recruitment agencies</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 2</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Advertising, Marketing & Public Relations</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Advertising or marketing the business of the data controller, activity, goods or services and promoting public relations in connection with that business or activity, or those goods or services.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Customers and Clients<br>Complainants, correspondents and enquirers</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Goods or Services Provided</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Traders in personal data</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 3</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Accounts & Records</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Keeping accounts related to any business or other activity carried on by the data controller, or deciding whether to accept any person as a customer or supplier, or keeping records of purchases, sales or other transactions for the purpose of ensuring that the requisite payments and deliveries are made or services provided by him or to him in respect of those transactions, or for the purpose of making financial or management forecasts to assist him in the conduct of any such business or activity</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Customers and Clients<br>Suppliers<br>Complainants, correspondents and enquirers</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Financial Details<br>Goods or Services Provided</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Other companies in the same group as the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Financial organisations and advisers<br>Credit reference agencies<br>Debt collection and tracing agencies<br>Central Government</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 4</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Trading / Sharing in Personal Information</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>The sale, hire or exchange of personal information.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Customers and Clients<br>Complainants, correspondents and enquirers</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Financial Details<br>Goods or Services Provided</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Other companies in the same group as the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Traders in personal data</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 5</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Crime Prevention and Prosecution of Offenders</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Crime prevention and detection and the apprehension and prosecution of offenders.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Controllers further description of Purpose:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>INCLUDES USE OF CLOSED-CIRCUIT TELEVISION FOR THE MONITORING AND COLLECTION<br>OF SOUND AND/OR VISUAL IMAGES FOR THE PURPOSE OF MAINTAINING THE SECURITY<br>OF PREMISES, FOR PREVENTING CRIME AND INVESTIGATING CRIME.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Customers and Clients<br>Offenders and suspected offenders</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>MEMBERS OF THE PUBLIC<br>THOSE INSIDE, ENTERING OR IN THE IMMEDIATE VICINITY OF THE AREA UNDER SURVEILLAN</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Goods or Services Provided<br>Offences (Including Alleged Offences)<br>Criminal Proceedings, Outcomes And Sentences.</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>SOUND AND/OR VISUAL IMAGES<br>PERSONAL APPEARANCE AND BEHAVIOUR</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>SECURITY ORGANISATIONS</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Persons making an enquiry or complaint<br>Police forces</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z9461069</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>GRESHAM INSURANCE COMPANY LIMITED</Organisation_name>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>8 SURREY STREET</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>NORWICH</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_postcode>NR1 3NG</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-05-04</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-05-03</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>N</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<B><FONT size=2 face=verdana><P>Nature of work - Insurance Company</P></B> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Description of processing</P></B> <P>The following is a broad description of the way this organisation/data controller processes personal information. To understand how your own personal information is processed you may need to refer to any personal communications you have received, check any privacy notices the organisation has provided or contact the organisation to ask about your personal circumstances. </P><B> <P><Br></P> <P>Reasons/purposes for processing information</P></B> <P>We process personal information to enable us to administer insurance business and provide financial services; promote our services; maintain our accounts and records and support and manage our employees.</P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Type/classes of information processed</P></B> <P>We process information relevant to the above reasons/purposes. This may include:</P> <UL> <LI>personal details</LI> <LI>family details</LI> <LI>lifestyle and social circumstances</LI> <LI>education and employment details</LI> <LI>business activities of the person whose personal data we are processing</LI> <LI>financial details</LI> <LI>goods or services provided</LI></UL> <P><Br></P> <P>We also process sensitive classes of information that may include: </P> <UL> <LI>racial or ethnic origin</LI> <LI>religious or other beliefs</LI> <LI>trade union membership</LI> <LI>physical or mental health details</LI> <LI>sexual life</LI> <LI>criminal proceedings, outcomes and sentences</LI> <LI>offences and alleged offences </LI></UL> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information is processed about</P></B> <P>We process personal information about: </P> <UL> <LI>our clients</LI> <LI>employees</LI> <LI>complainants, enquirers</LI> <LI>professional advisers</LI> <LI>suppliers and service providers</LI> <LI>offenders and suspected offenders</LI></UL> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information may be shared with</P></B> <P>We sometimes need to share the personal information we process with the individual themself and also with other organisations. Where this is necessary we are required to comply with all aspects of the Data Protection Act (DPA). What follows is a description of the types of organisations we may need to share some of the personal information we process with for one or more reasons. </P> <P><Br></P> <P>Where necessary or required we share information with: </P> <UL> <LI>family, associates and representatives of the person whose personal data we are processing</LI> <LI>current, past and prospective employers</LI> <LI>employment and recruitment agencies</LI> <LI>educators and examining bodies</LI> <LI>financial organisations</LI> <LI>credit reference agencies</LI> <LI>healthcare, social and welfare organisations</LI> <LI>credit reference agencies</LI> <LI>central government</LI> <LI>ombudsman and regulatory authorities</LI> <LI>police forces</LI> <LI>claims investigators</LI> <LI>suppliers and service providers</LI></UL></FONT><P><BR></P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><B>
<P>CCTV - Crime Prevention and/or Staff Monitoring </B></P>
<P>CCTV is used for maintaining the security of property and premises and for preventing and investigating crime, it may also be used to monitor staff when carrying out work duties. For these reasons the information processed may include visual images, personal appearance and behaviours. This information may be about staff, customers and clients, offenders and suspected offenders, members of the public and those inside, entering or in the immediate vicinity of the area under surveillance. Where necessary or required this information is shared with the data subjects themselves, employees and agents, services providers, police forces, security organisations and persons making an enquiry.</P></FONT><P><BR></P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><B>
<P>Providing Financial Services and Advice</B></P>
<P>Personal information is also processed in order to provide financial services and advice. For this reason the information processed may include name, contact details, family details, lifestyle and social circumstances, financial details, goods and services and sensitive classes of information that may include physical or mental health details. This information may be about clients, family and associates of clients, suppliers and enquirers. Where necessary or required this information is shared with the data subjects themselves, professional advisers and consultants, services providers, credit reference agencies.</P></FONT><P><Br></P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><B> <P>Undertaking Research </P></B><P>Personal information is also processed in order to undertake research. For this reason the information processed may include name, contact details, family details, lifestyle and social circumstances, financial details, good and services. The sensitive types of information may include physical or mental health details, racial or ethnic origin and religious or other beliefs. This information is about survey respondents. Where necessary or required this information may be shared with customers and clients, agents, service providers, survey and research organisations.</P></FONT><B><FONT size=2 face=verdana>
<P><BR></P>
<P>Transfers</P>
<P></B>It may sometimes be necessary to transfer personal information overseas. When this is needed information may be transferred to countries or territories around the world. Any transfers made will be in full compliance with all aspects of the data protection act.</P></FONT>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z9461055</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>SILK COCOON LIMITED</Organisation_name>
    <Companies_House_number>4226955</Companies_House_number>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>44 MERRIVALE SQUARE</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>OXFORD</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_postcode>OX2 6QX</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-05-03</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-05-02</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>N</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 1</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff Administration</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Appointments or removals, pay, discipline, superannuation, work management or other personnel matters in relation to the staff of the data controller.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff including volunteers, agents, temporary and casual workers<br>Relatives, guardians and associates of the data subject</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Education and Training Details<br>Employment Details<br>Financial Details<br>Racial or Ethnic Origin<br>Religious or Other Beliefs Of A Similar Nature<br>Trade Union Membership<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Relatives, guardians or other persons associated with the data subject<br>Current, past or prospective employers of the data subject<br>Education, training establishments and examining bodies<br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Financial organisations and advisers<br>Central Government<br>Employment and recruitment agencies</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 2</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Advertising, Marketing & Public Relations</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Advertising or marketing the business of the data controller, activity, goods or services and promoting public relations in connection with that business or activity, or those goods or services.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Customers and Clients<br>Complainants, correspondents and enquirers</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Goods or Services Provided</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Traders in personal data</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 3</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Accounts & Records</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Keeping accounts related to any business or other activity carried on by the data controller, or deciding whether to accept any person as a customer or supplier, or keeping records of purchases, sales or other transactions for the purpose of ensuring that the requisite payments and deliveries are made or services provided by him or to him in respect of those transactions, or for the purpose of making financial or management forecasts to assist him in the conduct of any such business or activity</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Customers and Clients<br>Suppliers<br>Complainants, correspondents and enquirers</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Financial Details<br>Goods or Services Provided</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Other companies in the same group as the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Financial organisations and advisers<br>Credit reference agencies<br>Debt collection and tracing agencies<br>Central Government</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Worldwide</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 4</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Trading / Sharing in Personal Information</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>The sale, hire or exchange of personal information.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Customers and Clients<br>Complainants, correspondents and enquirers</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Financial Details<br>Goods or Services Provided</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Other companies in the same group as the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Traders in personal data</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 5</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Crime Prevention and Prosecution of Offenders</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Crime prevention and detection and the apprehension and prosecution of offenders.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Controllers further description of Purpose:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>INCLUDES USE OF CLOSED-CIRCUIT TELEVISION FOR THE MONITORING AND COLLECTION<br>OF SOUND AND/OR VISUAL IMAGES FOR THE PURPOSE OF MAINTAINING THE SECURITY<br>OF PREMISES, FOR PREVENTING CRIME AND INVESTIGATING CRIME.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Customers and Clients<br>Offenders and suspected offenders</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>MEMBERS OF THE PUBLIC<br>THOSE INSIDE, ENTERING OR IN THE IMMEDIATE VICINITY OF THE AREA UNDER SURVEILLAN</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Goods or Services Provided<br>Offences (Including Alleged Offences)<br>Criminal Proceedings, Outcomes And Sentences.</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>SOUND AND/OR VISUAL IMAGES<br>PERSONAL APPEARANCE AND BEHAVIOUR</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>SECURITY ORGANISATIONS</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Persons making an enquiry or complaint<br>Police forces</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z9460995</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>LIBANUS PRIMARY SCHOOL</Organisation_name>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>LIBANUS ROAD</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>BLACKWOOD</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_3>GWENT</Organisation_address_line_3>
    <Organisation_postcode>NP12 1EH</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-10-02</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-10-01</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>Y</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<B><FONT size=2 face=verdana><P>Nature of work - School</P></B> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Description of processing</P></B> <P>The following is a broad description of the way this organisation/data controller processes personal information. To understand how your own personal information is processed you may need to refer to any personal communications you have received, check any privacy notices the organisation has provided or contact the organisation to ask about your personal circumstances. </P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Reasons/purposes for processing information</P></B> <P>We process personal information to enable us to:</P> <P>provide education, training, welfare and educational support services</P> <P>administer school property</P> <P>maintain our own accounts and records</P> <P>carry out fundraising</P> <P>support and manage our employees </P> <P><Br></P> <P>We also use CCTV systems to monitor and collect visual images for security and the prevention of crime. </P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Type/classes of information processed</P></B> <P>We process information relating to the above reasons/purposes. This information may include:</P> <UL> <LI>name and personal details</LI> <LI>family, lifestyle and social circumstances</LI> <LI>financial details</LI> <LI>education details</LI> <LI>employment details</LI> <LI>student and disciplinary records</LI> <LI>vetting checks</LI> <LI>goods and services</LI> <LI>visual images, personal appearance and behaviour</LI></UL> <P><Br></P> <P>We also process sensitive classes of information that may include:</P> <UL> <LI>physical or mental health details</LI> <LI>racial or ethnic origin</LI> <LI>religious or other beliefs of a similar nature</LI> <LI>trade union membership</LI> <LI>sexual life</LI> <LI>offences and alleged offences</LI></UL> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information is processed about</P></B> <P>We process personal information about:</P> <UL> <LI>our students and pupils</LI> <LI>advisers and other professional experts</LI> <LI>school staff</LI> <LI>members of school boards</LI> <LI>donors and potential donors</LI> <LI>suppliers</LI> <LI>complainants and enquirers</LI> <LI>individuals captured by CCTV images </LI></UL> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information may be shared with</P></B> <P>We sometimes need to share the personal information we process with the individual themself and also with other organisations. Where this is necessary we are required to comply with all aspects of the Data Protection Act (DPA). What follows is a description of the types of organisations we may need to share some of the personal information we process with for one or more reasons. </P> <P><Br></P> <P>Where necessary or required we share information with:</P> <UL> <LI>education, training, careers and examining bodies</LI> <LI>school staff and boards</LI> <LI>family, associates and representatives of the person whose personal data we are processing</LI> <LI>local and central government</LI> <LI>healthcare professionals</LI> <LI>social and welfare organisations</LI> <LI>police forces</LI> <LI>courts</LI> <LI>current, past or prospective employers</LI> <LI>voluntary and charitable organisations</LI> <LI>business associates and other professional advisers</LI> <LI>suppliers and service providers</LI> <LI>financial organisations</LI> <LI>security organisations</LI> <LI>press and the media</LI></UL></FONT><P><BR></P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><B>
<P>Trading and Sharing Personal Information</B></P>
<P>Personal information is traded and shared as a primary business function. For this reason the information processed may include name, contact details, family details, financial details, employment details, and goods and services. This information may be about customers and clients. The information may be traded or shared with business associates and professional advisers, agents, service providers, customers and clients, and traders in personal data.</P></FONT><B><FONT size=2 face=verdana>
<P><BR></P>
<P>Transfers</P>
<P></B>It may sometimes be necessary to transfer personal information overseas. When this is needed information may be transferred to countries or territories around the world. Any transfers made will be in full compliance with all aspects of the data protection act.</P></FONT>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z9460964</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>KINGS FARM PRIMARY SCHOOL</Organisation_name>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>CEDAR AVENUE</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>GRAVESEND</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_3>KENT</Organisation_address_line_3>
    <Organisation_postcode>DA12 5JT</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>Y</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-06-22</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-06-21</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>N</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<B><FONT size=2 face=verdana><P>Nature of work - School</P></B> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Description of processing</P></B> <P>The following is a broad description of the way this organisation/data controller processes personal information. To understand how your own personal information is processed you may need to refer to any personal communications you have received, check any privacy notices the organisation has provided or contact the organisation to ask about your personal circumstances. </P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Reasons/purposes for processing information</P></B> <P>We process personal information to enable us to:</P> <P>provide education, training, welfare and educational support services</P> <P>administer school property</P> <P>maintain our own accounts and records</P> <P>carry out fundraising</P> <P>support and manage our employees </P> <P><Br></P> <P>We also use CCTV systems to monitor and collect visual images for security and the prevention of crime. </P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Type/classes of information processed</P></B> <P>We process information relating to the above reasons/purposes. This information may include:</P> <UL> <LI>name and personal details</LI> <LI>family, lifestyle and social circumstances</LI> <LI>financial details</LI> <LI>education details</LI> <LI>employment details</LI> <LI>student and disciplinary records</LI> <LI>vetting checks</LI> <LI>goods and services</LI> <LI>visual images, personal appearance and behaviour</LI></UL> <P><Br></P> <P>We also process sensitive classes of information that may include:</P> <UL> <LI>physical or mental health details</LI> <LI>racial or ethnic origin</LI> <LI>religious or other beliefs of a similar nature</LI> <LI>trade union membership</LI> <LI>sexual life</LI> <LI>offences and alleged offences</LI></UL> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information is processed about</P></B> <P>We process personal information about:</P> <UL> <LI>our students and pupils</LI> <LI>advisers and other professional experts</LI> <LI>school staff</LI> <LI>members of school boards</LI> <LI>donors and potential donors</LI> <LI>suppliers</LI> <LI>complainants and enquirers</LI> <LI>individuals captured by CCTV images </LI></UL> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information may be shared with</P></B> <P>We sometimes need to share the personal information we process with the individual themself and also with other organisations. Where this is necessary we are required to comply with all aspects of the Data Protection Act (DPA). What follows is a description of the types of organisations we may need to share some of the personal information we process with for one or more reasons. </P> <P><Br></P> <P>Where necessary or required we share information with:</P> <UL> <LI>education, training, careers and examining bodies</LI> <LI>school staff and boards</LI> <LI>family, associates and representatives of the person whose personal data we are processing</LI> <LI>local and central government</LI> <LI>healthcare professionals</LI> <LI>social and welfare organisations</LI> <LI>police forces</LI> <LI>courts</LI> <LI>current, past or prospective employers</LI> <LI>voluntary and charitable organisations</LI> <LI>business associates and other professional advisers</LI> <LI>suppliers and service providers</LI> <LI>financial organisations</LI> <LI>security organisations</LI> <LI>press and the media</LI></UL></FONT><P><BR></P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><B>
<P>Trading and Sharing Personal Information</B></P>
<P>Personal information is traded and shared as a primary business function. For this reason the information processed may include name, contact details, family details, financial details, employment details, and goods and services. This information may be about customers and clients. The information may be traded or shared with business associates and professional advisers, agents, service providers, customers and clients, and traders in personal data.</P></FONT><B><FONT size=2 face=verdana>
<P><BR></P>
<P>Transfers</P>
<P></B>It may sometimes be necessary to transfer personal information overseas. When this is needed information may be transferred to countries or territories around the world. Any transfers made will be in full compliance with all aspects of the data protection act.</P></FONT>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z9460950</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>HR ACCESS SOLUTIONS UK LIMITED</Organisation_name>
    <Companies_House_number>05707552</Companies_House_number>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>5TH FLOOR CONDOR HOUSE</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>10 ST PAUL'S CHURCHYARD</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_4>LONDON</Organisation_address_line_4>
    <Organisation_postcode>EC4M 8AL</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-05-16</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-05-15</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>N</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<B><FONT size=2 face=verdana><P>Nature of work - General business </P> <P></B></P><B> <P>Description of processing</P></B> <P>The following is a broad description of the way this organisation/data controller processes personal information. To understand how your own personal information is processed you may need to refer to any personal communications you have received, check any privacy notices the organisation has provided or contact the organisation to ask about your personal circumstances. </P><B> <P><Br></P> <P>Reasons/purposes for processing information</P></B> <P>We process personal information to enable us to promote our goods and services, to maintain our accounts and records and to support and manage our staff. </P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Type/classes of information processed</P></B> <P>We process information relevant to the above reasons/purposes. This may include:</P> <UL> <LI>personal details</LI> <LI>family, lifestyle and social circumstances</LI> <LI>financial details</LI> <LI>employment and education details</LI> <LI>goods or services provided</LI></UL> <P><Br></P> <P>We also process sensitive classes of information that may include:</P> <UL> <LI>physical or mental health details</LI> <LI>racial or ethnic origin</LI> <LI>religious or other beliefs of a similar nature</LI> <LI>trade union membership</LI></UL> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information is processed about</P></B> <P>We process personal information about our:</P> <UL> <LI>employees</LI> <LI>customers and clients</LI> <LI>suppliers and services providers</LI> <LI>advisers, consultants and other professional experts</LI> <LI>complainants and enquirers</LI></UL> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information may be shared with</P></B> <P>We sometimes need to share the personal information we process with the individual themself and also with other organisations. Where this is necessary we are required to comply with all aspects of the Data Protection Act (DPA). What follows is a description of the types of organisations we may need to share some of the personal information we process with for one or more reasons. </P> <P><Br></P> <P>Where necessary or required we share information with:</P> <UL> <LI>family, associates and representatives of the person whose personal data we are processing</LI> <LI>employment and recruitment agencies</LI> <LI>current, past and prospective employers</LI> <LI>educators and examining bodies</LI> <LI>central government</LI> <LI>credit reference agencies</LI> <LI>suppliers and service providers</LI> <LI>debt collection and tracing agencies</LI> <LI>financial organisations</LI></UL></FONT><B><FONT size=2 face=verdana>
<P><BR></P>
<P>Transfers</B></P>
<P>It may sometimes be necessary to transfer personal information overseas. When this is needed information is only shared within the European Economic Area (EEA). Any transfers made will be in full compliance with all aspects of the data protection act.</P></FONT>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z9460933</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>KINGDOM SECURITY LIMITED</Organisation_name>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>MILL BROW</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>ECCLESTON</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_3>ST. HELENS</Organisation_address_line_3>
    <Organisation_address_line_4>MERSEYSIDE</Organisation_address_line_4>
    <Organisation_postcode>WA10 4QG</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-06-27</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-06-26</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>N</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<B><FONT size=2 face=verdana><P>Nature of work - General business </P> <P></B></P><B> <P>Description of processing</P></B> <P>The following is a broad description of the way this organisation/data controller processes personal information. To understand how your own personal information is processed you may need to refer to any personal communications you have received, check any privacy notices the organisation has provided or contact the organisation to ask about your personal circumstances. </P><B> <P><Br></P> <P>Reasons/purposes for processing information</P></B> <P>We process personal information to enable us to promote our goods and services, to maintain our accounts and records and to support and manage our staff. </P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Type/classes of information processed</P></B> <P>We process information relevant to the above reasons/purposes. This may include:</P> <UL> <LI>personal details</LI> <LI>family, lifestyle and social circumstances</LI> <LI>financial details</LI> <LI>employment and education details</LI> <LI>goods or services provided</LI></UL> <P><Br></P> <P>We also process sensitive classes of information that may include:</P> <UL> <LI>physical or mental health details</LI> <LI>racial or ethnic origin</LI> <LI>religious or other beliefs of a similar nature</LI> <LI>trade union membership</LI></UL> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information is processed about</P></B> <P>We process personal information about our:</P> <UL> <LI>employees</LI> <LI>customers and clients</LI> <LI>suppliers and services providers</LI> <LI>advisers, consultants and other professional experts</LI> <LI>complainants and enquirers</LI></UL> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information may be shared with</P></B> <P>We sometimes need to share the personal information we process with the individual themself and also with other organisations. Where this is necessary we are required to comply with all aspects of the Data Protection Act (DPA). What follows is a description of the types of organisations we may need to share some of the personal information we process with for one or more reasons. </P> <P><Br></P> <P>Where necessary or required we share information with:</P> <UL> <LI>family, associates and representatives of the person whose personal data we are processing</LI> <LI>employment and recruitment agencies</LI> <LI>current, past and prospective employers</LI> <LI>educators and examining bodies</LI> <LI>central government</LI> <LI>credit reference agencies</LI> <LI>suppliers and service providers</LI> <LI>debt collection and tracing agencies</LI> <LI>financial organisations</LI></UL></FONT><B><FONT size=2 face=verdana>
<P><BR></P>
<P>Transfers</B></P>
<P>It may sometimes be necessary to transfer personal information overseas. When this is needed information is only shared within the European Economic Area (EEA). Any transfers made will be in full compliance with all aspects of the data protection act.</P></FONT>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z946092X</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>TOMA GLOBAL LIMITED</Organisation_name>
    <Companies_House_number>04584496</Companies_House_number>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>333 EARLSFIELD ROAD</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>LONDON</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_postcode>SW18 3DG</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-05-10</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-05-09</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>N</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<B><FONT size=2 face=verdana><P>Nature of work - Software Development</P></B> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Description of processing</P></B> <P>The following is a broad description of the way this organisation/data controller processes personal information. To understand how your own personal information is processed you may need to refer to any personal communications you have received, check any privacy notices the organisation has provided or contact the organisation to ask about your personal circumstances. </P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Reasons/purposes for processing information</P></B> <P>We process personal information to enable us to provide a service in which we design, test and demonstrate software; promote our services; maintain our accounts and records and to manage our staff.</P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Type/classes of information processed</P></B> <P>We process information relevant to the above reasons/purposes. This may include:</P> <UL> <LI>personal details</LI> <LI>family details</LI> <LI>lifestyle and social circumstances</LI> <LI>goods and services</LI> <LI>employment and education details</LI> <LI>financial details</LI> <LI>information necessary for the development and test of software</LI></UL> <P><Br></P> <P>We also process sensitive classes of information that may include physical or mental health details; racial or ethnic origin; religious or other beliefs.</P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information is processed about</P></B> <P>We process personal information about our clients, employees, suppliers and individuals necessary for software development.</P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information may be shared with</P></B> <P>We sometimes need to share the personal information we process with the individual themself and also with other organisations. Where this is necessary we are required to comply with all aspects of the Data Protection Act (DPA). What follows is a description of the types of organisations we may need to share some of the personal information we process with for one or more reasons. </P> <P><Br></P> <P>Where necessary or required we share information with: </P> <UL> <LI>family, associates and representatives of the person whose personal data we are processing</LI> <LI>suppliers and service providers</LI> <LI>professional advisers and consultants</LI> <LI>financial organisations</LI> <LI>credit reference agencies</LI> <LI>debt collection and tracing agencies</LI> <LI>employment and recruitment agencies</LI> <LI>central government</LI></UL></FONT><B><FONT size=2 face=verdana>
<P><BR></P>
<P>Transfers</B></P>
<P>It may sometimes be necessary to transfer personal information overseas. When this is needed information is only shared within the European Economic Area (EEA). Any transfers made will be in full compliance with all aspects of the data protection act.</P></FONT>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z9460902</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>ST PETERS C E PRIMARY SCHOOL</Organisation_name>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>VICARAGE ROAD</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>SWINTON</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_3>MANCHESTER</Organisation_address_line_3>
    <Organisation_postcode>M27 0WA</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>Y</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-05-05</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-05-04</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>N</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 1</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Education</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>The provision of education or training as a primary function or as a business activity.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Controllers further description of Purpose:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>ADMINISTRATION OF EDUCATION AND TRAINING (E.G. REGISTRATION,<br>MONITORING AND REPORTING, CALCULATION AND PUBLICATION OF EXAM<br>RESULTS, PROVISION OF REFERENCES)<br>PROVISION OF EDUCATION AND TRAINING (E.G. PLANNING AND CONTROL OF<br>CURRICULA AND EXAMS, COMMISSIONING, VALIDATION AND PRODUCING<br>EDUCATIONAL MATERIALS, ARRANGEMENT OF WORK EXPERIENCE PLACEMENTS)<br>PREPARATION OF DFES RETURNS</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff including volunteers, agents, temporary and casual workers<br>Suppliers<br>Relatives, guardians and associates of the data subject<br>Students and pupils</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Employment Details<br>Financial Details<br>Goods or Services Provided<br>Racial or Ethnic Origin<br>Religious or Other Beliefs Of A Similar Nature<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>STUDENT RECORDS<br>DISCIPLINARY RECORDS</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>DFES</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Relatives, guardians or other persons associated with the data subject<br>Current, past or prospective employers of the data subject<br>Healthcare, social and welfare advisers or practitioners<br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Data processors</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 2</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Educational Support and Ancillary Purposes</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Controllers further description of Purpose:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>TO INCLUDE PROCESSING FOR PURPOSES SUPPLEMENTARY TO THE<br>PROVISION OF EDUCATION AND TRAINING<br>ADMINISTRATION AND PROVISION OF HEALTH CARE SERVICES<br>ADMINISTRATION AND PROVISION OF WELFARE AND PASTORAL SERVICES<br>ADMINISTRATION AND PROVISION OF LIBRARY SERVICES (INCLUDING<br>MEMBERSHIP RECORDS, LOAN/HIRE RECORDS, INFORMATION AND DATABANK<br>ADMINISTRATION)<br>CAREERS GUIDANCE<br>PLANNING AND ADMINISTRATION OF EVENTS (E.G. SOCIAL, SPORTS, SCHOOL<br>TRIPS ETC.)<br>ORGANISATION OF PARENT-TEACHERS AND OTHER ASSOCIATIONS AND EVENTS<br>INVOLVING PARENTS/GUARDIANS OF PUPILS<br>ORGANISATION OF ALUMNI AND OTHER ASSOCIATIONS AND EVENTS INVOLVING<br>FORMER PUPILS AND STUDENTS</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff including volunteers, agents, temporary and casual workers<br>Suppliers<br>Complainants, correspondents and enquirers<br>Relatives, guardians and associates of the data subject<br>Advisers, consultants and other professional experts<br>Students and pupils<br>School staff, members of school boards / boards of governors</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>HEALTH PROFESSIONALS<br>WELFARE AND PASTORAL PROFESSIONALS AND ADVISORS<br>AUTHORS, PUBLISHERS, EDITORS, ARTISTS AND OTHER CREATORS</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Education and Training Details<br>Employment Details<br>Financial Details<br>Goods or Services Provided<br>Racial or Ethnic Origin<br>Religious or Other Beliefs Of A Similar Nature<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition<br>Sexual Life<br>Offences (Including Alleged Offences)</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>STUDENT RECORDS<br>DISCIPLINARY RECORDS</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Relatives, guardians or other persons associated with the data subject<br>Current, past or prospective employers of the data subject<br>Healthcare, social and welfare advisers or practitioners<br>Education, training establishments and examining bodies<br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Financial organisations and advisers<br>Police forces<br>Local Government<br>Courts / Tribunals<br>Careers service</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 3</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Schools Administration</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Controllers further description of Purpose:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>ADMINISTRATION AND MANAGEMENT OF SCHOOL PROPERTY<br>PLANNING AND ADMINISTRATION OF REPAIR AND MAINTENANCE, ACCESS,<br>SECURITY AND SAFETY ARRANGEMENTS<br>OFFICE ADMINISTRATION (INCLUDING OFFICE DIRECTORIES, E-MAIL,<br>WORD PROCESSING, DEALING WITH ENQUIRIES AND COMPLAINTS)<br>ADMINISTRATION IN CONNECTION WITH BOARD OF GOVERNORS ETC<br>THE ADMINISTRATION OF SUPPLIER RECORDS RELATING TO GOODS, ORDERS,<br>SERVICES AND ACCOUNTS PROVIDED TO THE SCHOOL</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff including volunteers, agents, temporary and casual workers<br>Suppliers<br>Relatives, guardians and associates of the data subject<br>Students and pupils<br>School staff, members of school boards / boards of governors</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Employment Details<br>Financial Details<br>Goods or Services Provided<br>Racial or Ethnic Origin<br>Religious or Other Beliefs Of A Similar Nature<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Relatives, guardians or other persons associated with the data subject<br>Current, past or prospective employers of the data subject<br>Healthcare, social and welfare advisers or practitioners<br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Data processors<br>School boards / school staff / boards of governors</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 4</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff, Agent and Contractor Administration</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Controllers further description of Purpose:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>THE ADMINISTRATION OF PROSPECTIVE, CURRENT AND PAST EMPLOYEES<br>INCLUDING SELF-EMPLOYED, CONTRACT PERSONNEL, TEMPORARY STAFF<br>OR VOLUNTARY WORKERS<br>PLANNING AND MANAGEMENT OF STAFF WORKLOAD AND/OR BUSINESS<br>ACTIVITIES<br>ADMINISTRATION OF AGENTS OR OTHER INTERMEDIARIES<br>VETTING  CHECKS<br>STAFF TRAINING<br>OCCUPATIONAL HEALTH SERVICE<br>PENSIONS ADMINISTRATION<br>DISCIPLINARY MATTERS, INDUSTRIAL TRIBUNALS ETC.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Staff including volunteers, agents, temporary and casual workers<br>Suppliers</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Employment Details<br>Financial Details<br>Goods or Services Provided</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Current, past or prospective employers of the data subject<br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 5</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Advertising, Marketing, Public Relations, General Advice Services</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Controllers further description of Purpose:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>ADVERTISEMENT, MARKETING AND PROMOTION OF THE SCHOOL BY<br>DIRECT MARKETING AND OTHER MEANS<br>THE PROVISION OF GENERAL INFORMATION  AND ADVICE TO MEMBERS OF<br>THE PUBLIC ABOUT THE SCHOOL AND THE SERVICES IT OFFERS<br>IDENTIFICATION OF POTENTIAL DONORS<br>FUNDRAISING BY DIRECT MARKETING AND OTHER METHODS</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Suppliers<br>Relatives, guardians and associates of the data subject<br>Students and pupils</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>PERSONS WHO MAY BE THE SUBJECT OF ENQUIRY, PRESS RELEASE OR OTHER<br>PROMOTIONAL EXERCISE<br>DONORS AND POTENTIAL DONORS</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Family, Lifestyle and Social Circumstances<br>Education and Training Details<br>Employment Details<br>Racial or Ethnic Origin<br>Religious or Other Beliefs Of A Similar Nature<br>Physical or Mental Health or Condition</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Relatives, guardians or other persons associated with the data subject<br>Current, past or prospective employers of the data subject<br>Healthcare, social and welfare advisers or practitioners<br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Data processors<br>School boards / school staff / boards of governors</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>OCCASIONAL WORLD-WIDE TRANSFERS IN CONNECTION WITH FUNDRAISING<br>CAMPAIGNS</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Worldwide</FONT></P><hr><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose 6</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Trading / Sharing in Personal Information</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Purpose Description:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>The sale, hire or exchange of personal information.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Controllers further description of Purpose:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>INCLUDES THE USE OF CLOSED-CIRCUIT TELEVISION FOR THE MONITORING<br>AND COLLECTION OF SOUND AND/OR VISUAL IMAGES FOR THE PURPOSE<br>OF MAINTAINING THE SECURITY OF PREMISES, FOR THE PREVENTING CRIME<br>AND FOR INVESTIGATING CRIME.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Subjects are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Customers and Clients<br>Offenders and suspected offenders</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>MEMBERS OF THE PUBLIC.<br>THOSES INSIDE, ENTERING OR IN THE IMMEDIATE VICINITY OF THE AREA<br>UNDER SURVEILLANCE.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Data Classes are:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>Personal Details<br>Goods or Services Provided<br>Offences (Including Alleged Offences)<br>Criminal Proceedings, Outcomes And Sentences.</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>SOUND AND/OR VISUAL IMAGES.</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Sources (S) and Disclosures (D)(1984 Act). Recipients(1998 Act):</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana>SECURITY ORGANISATIONS</FONT></P><br><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>Data subjects themselves<br>Business associates and other professional advisers<br>Employees and agents of the data controller<br>Suppliers, providers of goods or services<br>Persons making an enquiry or complaint<br>Police forces</FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><STRONG>Transfers:</STRONG></FONT></P><P><FONT size=2 face=verdana><br>None outside the European Economic Area</FONT></P><hr>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z9460887</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>P andAMP S BRADDOCK LIMITED</Organisation_name>
    <Companies_House_number>5564661</Companies_House_number>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>UNIT 6 CAROLINE COURT</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>BILLINGTON RD</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_3>BURNLEY</Organisation_address_line_3>
    <Organisation_postcode>BB11 5UB</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>N</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-05-10</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-05-09</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>N</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Trading_names>GREEN THUMB LAWN TREATMENT SERVICE</Trading_names>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<B><FONT size=2 face=verdana>
<P>Nature of work - General business. The Franchisor and other Franchisees forming part of the same Franchise Greenthumb.</P>
<P>&nbsp;</P>
<P></B></P><B>
<P>Description of processing</P></B>
<P>The following is a broad description of the way this organisation/data controller processes personal information. To understand how your own personal information is processed you may need to refer to any personal communications you have received, check any privacy notices the organisation has provided or contact the organisation to ask about your personal circumstances. </P><B>
<P><BR></P>
<P>Reasons/purposes for processing information</P></B>
<P>We process personal information to enable us to promote our goods and services, to maintain our accounts and records and to support and manage our staff. </P>
<P><BR></P><B>
<P>Type/classes of information processed</P></B>
<P>We process information relevant to the above reasons/purposes. This may include:</P>
<UL>
<LI>personal details 
<LI>family, lifestyle and social circumstances 
<LI>financial details 
<LI>employment and education details 
<LI>goods or services provided</LI></UL>
<P><BR></P>
<P>We also process sensitive classes of information that may include:</P>
<UL>
<LI>physical or mental health details 
<LI>racial or ethnic origin 
<LI>religious or other beliefs of a similar nature 
<LI>trade union membership</LI></UL>
<P><BR></P><B>
<P>Who the information is processed about</P></B>
<P>We process personal information about our:</P>
<UL>
<LI>employees 
<LI>customers and clients 
<LI>suppliers and services providers 
<LI>advisers, consultants and other professional experts 
<LI>complainants and enquirers</LI></UL>
<P><BR></P><B>
<P>Who the information may be shared with</P></B>
<P>We sometimes need to share the personal information we process with the individual themself and also with other organisations. Where this is necessary we are required to comply with all aspects of the Data Protection Act (DPA). What follows is a description of the types of organisations we may need to share some of the personal information we process with for one or more reasons. </P>
<P><BR></P>
<P>Where necessary or required we share information with:</P>
<UL>
<LI>family, associates and representatives of the person whose personal data we are processing 
<LI>employment and recruitment agencies 
<LI>current, past and prospective employers 
<LI>educators and examining bodies 
<LI>central government 
<LI>credit reference agencies 
<LI>suppliers and service providers 
<LI>debt collection and tracing agencies 
<LI>financial organisations</LI></UL></FONT><B><FONT size=2 face=verdana>
<P><BR></P>
<P>Transfers</B></P>
<P>It may sometimes be necessary to transfer personal information overseas. When this is needed information is only shared within the European Economic Area (EEA). Any transfers made will be in full compliance with all aspects of the data protection act.</P></FONT>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Registration_number>Z9460808</Registration_number>
    <Organisation_name>TARMINDER SINGH</Organisation_name>
    <Organisation_address_line_1>TSA DENTAL CARE</Organisation_address_line_1>
    <Organisation_address_line_2>5 DAVIES ROAD</Organisation_address_line_2>
    <Organisation_address_line_3>WEST BRIDGFORD</Organisation_address_line_3>
    <Organisation_address_line_4>NOTTINGHAM</Organisation_address_line_4>
    <Organisation_postcode>NG2 5JE</Organisation_postcode>
    <Organisation_country>UNITED KINGDOM</Organisation_country>
    <Freedom_of_Information_flag>Y</Freedom_of_Information_flag>
    <Start_date_of_registration>2006-07-03</Start_date_of_registration>
    <End_date_of_registration>2014-07-02</End_date_of_registration>
    <Exempt_processing_flag>Y</Exempt_processing_flag>
    <Contact_in_UK_C1>None</Contact_in_UK_C1>
    <Subject_access_Contact_C2>None</Subject_access_Contact_C2>
    <Nature_of_Work_description><![CDATA[<B><FONT size=2 face=verdana><P>Nature of work - Dentist</P></B><B> <P><Br></P> <P>Description of processing</P></B> <P>The following is a broad description of the way this organisation/data controller processes personal information. To understand how your own personal information is processed you may need to refer to any personal communications you have received, check any privacy notices the organisation has provided or contact the organisation to ask about your personal circumstances. </P><B> <P><Br></P> <P>Reasons/purposes for processing information</P></B> <P>We process personal information to enable us to provide healthcare services to our patients, maintain our own accounts and records, promote and advertise our services and to support and manage our employees. </P> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Type/classes of information processed</P></B> <P>We process information relevant to the above reasons/purposes. This information may include:</P> <UL> <LI>personal details</LI> <LI>family details</LI> <LI>lifestyle and social circumstances</LI> <LI>goods and services</LI> <LI>financial details</LI> <LI>education and employment details </LI></UL> <P><Br></P> <P>We also process sensitive classes of information that may include: </P> <UL> <LI>physical or mental health details</LI> <LI>racial or ethnic origin</LI> <LI>religious or other beliefs</LI> <LI>trade union membership</LI> <LI>sexual life</LI></UL> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information is processed about</P></B> <P>We process personal information about: </P> <UL> <LI>patients</LI> <LI>customers</LI> <LI>suppliers</LI> <LI>enquirers</LI> <LI>advisers, consultants other professional experts</LI> <LI>employees</LI></UL> <P><Br></P><B> <P>Who the information may be shared with</P></B> <P>We sometimes need to share the personal information we process with the individual themself and also with other organisations. Where this is necessary we are required to comply with all aspects of the Data Protection Act (DPA). What follows is a description of the types of organisations we may need to share some of the personal information we process with for one or more reasons. </P> <P><Br></P> <P>Where necessary or required we share information with: </P> <UL> <LI>healthcare professionals</LI> <LI>social and welfare organisations</LI> <LI>Dental Practice Board</LI> <LI>central government</LI> <LI>suppliers</LI> <LI>service providers</LI> <LI>survey and research organisations</LI> <LI>financial organisations</LI> <LI>current, past and prospective employers</LI> <LI>educators and examining bodies</LI> <LI>employees</LI> <LI>family, associates and representatives of the person whose personal data we are processing</LI></UL></FONT><B><FONT size=2 face=verdana>
<P><BR></P>
<P>Transfers</B></P>
<P>It may sometimes be necessary to transfer personal information overseas. When this is needed information is only shared within the European Economic Area (EEA). Any transfers made will be in full compliance with all aspects of the data protection act.</P></FONT>]]></Nature_of_Work_description>
  </Record>
